Escape to Magic Camp!
Magic Camp is a family, fantasy, comedy film directed by Mark Waters.
Andy, at the urging of his former mentor and Magic Camp owner Roy Preston,
returns to the camp of his youth hoping to reignite his career.
Instead, he finds inspiration in his ragtag bunch of rookie magicians.
Andy Tuckerman, played by Adam Devine.
Roy Preston, played by Jeffrey Tambor.
Christina Darkwood, played by Gillian Jacobs.
Theo, played by Nathaniel Logan McIntyre.
Nathan, played by Cole Sand.
Ruth, played by Isabella Crovetti.
Magic Camp is a 2020 American fantasy comedy
family film directed by Mark Waters.
Micah Fitzerman-Blue, Noah Harpster, Matt Spicer, Max Winkler, Dan Gregor and Doug Mand serve as
co-screenwriters, with an original story written by Gabe Sachs, Jeff Judah, Spicer and Winkler.
It stars Adam DeVine, Jeffrey Tambor and Gillian Jacobs.
The film was released on Disney+ on August 14, 2020.
The film was removed from Disney+ on May 26, 2023.
The tone is lighthearted.